I wish I had known that before
I posted all those pictures on Facebook.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)All right. Let's hit the road. I wouldn't mind
shooting some ducks in the morning.
(Howard:)Wait, now we're shooting things?
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)I like using a big shell.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)You can't eat them afterwards
but it's fun watching them blow up.
(Howard:)Sir, I'm flattered that you invited me
and I really want you to like me...
(Howard:)...but I don't think this trip is the way to do it.
(Howard:)And I can't return these things
if there's chunks of duck all over them.
- So why'd you agree to come?
- Because Bernadette made me.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)I tried to back out too.
My wife said I had to go.
(Howard:)Really? Your wife makes you do stuff?
You're a big, scary cop.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)You're an astronaut
and your wife makes you do things...